<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="primary_content_headings">
        <item>Layouts</item>
        <item>View Components - 1</item>
        <item>View Components - 2</item>
        <item>Palette</item>
        <item>Styles, Themes and Backward Compatibility</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="primary_content_description">
        <item><![CDATA[
<p>
This part deals with material design recommended layouts to structure the content of application.
Contains demo samples for seams, steps, 8dp rythms, elevations, shadows, metrics and region
</p>
<ul>
<li> Create layouts by combining papers that are attached to each other (seams)</li>
<li> Arrange papers in steps (elevations) </li>
<li> Play with elevations and shadows </li>
<li> Understand 8dp rhythm in various layouts </li>
<li> Get to know recommended metrics </li>
<li> Explore different regions in an app screen </li>
</ul>
]]></item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
<p>
This part explores in depth material components like Buttons, Floating Action Button, Card View and Snackbar. Contains demos that delve into various aspects of these components and available customizations. In the workshop there will be hands on coding developing each of these components.
</p>
<p>
  <b> Button </b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand material design sepcification for Button.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore different states of Button. Raised buttons, floating buttons and flat buttons.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore different customizations available for buttons.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Backward compatibility with AppCompat library.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>
<p>
  <b> Floating Action Button </b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Explore specification for FAB, understand when and how to use it.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore placement, appearance and disapperance of FAB.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore various FAB transitions like speed Dial transition, tabbed layout transition, toolbar transition and custom transitions.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore FABs that can be morphed into another view.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Compat library support.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>
<p>
  <b> Card View </b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand specification for Cards.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Cards in list view, recycler view and view groups.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Play with elevation, rounding and content padding in cards.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore various actions on cards.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Compat library support.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>
<p>
  <b> Snackbar </b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand specification for Snackbar.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Snackbar appearance and disappearance.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Snackbar with and without action.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>
]]>
</item>
        <item>
<![CDATA[
<p>
This part explores in depth material components like AppBar, Toolbar, Collapsible Toolbar, Coordinator Layout, Navigation View, Floating Labels.
Contains demos that delve into various aspects of these components and available customizations. In the workshop there will be hands on coding developing each of these components.
</p>
<p>
  <b> App bar </b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand material design sepcification for App bar.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore different customizations available for App bar.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>
<p>
  <b> Toolbar </b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand toolbar widget and its setup via menu xml.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore different customizations available for Toolbar.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Play with placements of toolbar at various places in the screen layout.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>
<p>
  <b> Collapsible Toolbar </b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand Collapsible Toolbar widget and its setup via menu xml.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore different collapsing options available for Collapsible Toolbar.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>

<p>
  <b> Coordinator Layout</b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand Coordinator Layout concepts.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Explore and write new implementation for coordinator behaviour.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>

<p>
  <b> Navigation View</b>
  	<ul>
  		<li>
  			Understand using navigation view to build menu drawers.
  		</li>
  		<li>
  			Use xmls to inflate content into menu.
  		</li>
  	</ul>
</p>
]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[
<p>
A detailed exploration of Palette library is covered with hands on coding.
</p>
<ul>
<li> Build palette from a bitmap and extract colors.</li>
<li> Tint appbar, status bar and other views with extracted color palette. </li>
</ul>
]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[
<p>
In this part we will be exploring how to apply styling and customize all the widgets discussed in previous sections for maximum backward compatibility
</p>
]]></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
